Guide to the Edgar Odell Lovett and Mary Ellen Hale Lovett Family papers, 1849-1979 MS 494
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IV: Printed materials, 1885-1973, 219334
  - Printed programs, legal briefs, pamphlets, short stories, 219336 (Box 45, Folder -)
  - Blank postcards gathered by Mary Hale Lovett while traveling, 219335 (Box 46, Folder -)
- Series V: Community Involvement and Financial records, 1890-1951, 219270
  - Art League, 219322
    - Conventions, 1926-1935, 219333 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Convention in Houston, 1926, 219332 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Exhibits, 1924-1935, 219331 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Membership records, 1920-1939, 219330 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Newsclippings, 1923-1929, 219329 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Newsletters, 1923-1939, 219328 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Two books of letters pertaining to Art League, 1925-1926, 219327 (Box 47, Folder -)
    - Correspondence, 1924-1926, 219326 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1927-1928, 219325 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1929, 219324 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1930-1931, 1939, n.d., 219323 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Arts related newsclippings, brochures, 1925-1929, 219321 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Misc. clippings regarding women's involvement in arts, civics, 1925-1930, 219320 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Houston Museum of Art clippings, 1926, 219319 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Houston Museum of Art clippings, 1927-1929, 219318 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Houston Museum of Art correspondence, notices, 1916, 1926-1927, n.d., 219317 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Houston Museum of Art brochures, 1926-1939, 219316 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Houston Museum of Art correspondence, 1929 and 1937, 219315 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Edgar Odell Lovett insurance papers, 1928, 219314 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Banking, taxes, 1920, 219313 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Concerning Curlee Co., Mayfield, KY, 1933, 219312 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Business letters, 1933-1941, 219311 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Banking and taxes, 1935, 219310 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Income tax, 1936, 219309 (Box 50, Folder 6-7)
  - Income tax, 1937, 219308 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - H.S. Hale estate statements, 1937, 219307 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Business letters and bank statements, 1937, 219306 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Income tax, 1938, 219305 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Business letters from Theodore Hale, bank statements, etc., 1940-41, 219304 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Banking, 1941, 219303 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Income tax, 1942, 219302 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Income tax, 1943, 219301 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Financial records, 1943, 219300 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Financial records, 1945, 219299 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Income tax, 1945, 219298 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Banking and bills, 1946, 219297 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Texas and bank records, 1946-1950, 219296 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Financial records, 1947, 219295 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Banking, 1948, 219294 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Bank statements, 1949, 1951, 219293 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Bank statements, 1947-1948, 219292 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Bank account, Jan. 1948, 219291 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - H.S. Hale materials, 219271
    - Banking examples, 1890s-1950, 219290 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Banking and business, 1908-1915, 219289 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Business letters, 1916-1920, 219288 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Banking and business, 1925-1936, 219287 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Alexander's Guardians Trust, 1926-1928, 219286 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - First National Bank, Mayfield, KY, 1926-1927, 219285 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - First National Bank, Mayfield, KY, cheque stubs, 1927-1940, n.d., 219284 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Bank papers, 1929-1930, 219283 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - American Provident Life Insurance Co. stock, 1931, 219282 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Receipts and business letters from Theodore Hale, 1932, 219281 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Receipts and business letters from Theodore Hale, 1932-1940, 219280 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Receipts and business letters from Theodore Hale, 1933-1940, 219279 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Bank papers, 1938-1939, 219278 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Bank stock, 1944, 219277 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Income tax paper, 1945, 219276 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Sale of Hale homestead, 1945, 219275 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Bills, 1905-1916, 219274 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bills, receipts, ca. 1908-1920, 219273 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Notebook of financial information, 219272 (Box 52, Folder -)
- Series VI: Personal materials and realia, 1907-1977 (Boxes 53-66), 219214
  - Princeton and Rice: printed papers and comments, 1920s-1930s, 219269 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Princeton newsclippings, 1954, 219268 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Princeton commencement program, 1954 (E.O. Lovett's honorary degree), 219267 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Sightseeing, programs, invitations: Paris trip, 1921-1922, 219266 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Expenses and misc.: Paris trip, 1921-1922, 219265 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Pamphlets for events, ticket stubs, pre-voyage telegrams, Paris 1937, 219264 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Musicals, socials, ca. 1907-1954, 219263 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Family newsclippings, 219256
    - E.O. Lovett and family, 1940s-1970s, 219262 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - 1908, 1950s, 219261 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Lectures, Rice and other, 1913-1917, 1947, 219260 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Lovett and Wicks families, 1928-1951, 219259 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Wicks family, 219258 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Lovett family, 1928-1963, 219257 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Wicks family property, 1928, 1932, 1944, 219255 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Speeches, religious and personal materials, ca. 1910s-1920s, 219254 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Early Rice Institute materials, 219253 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Rice Institute Formal Opening, 219252 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Friends of Fondren Library materials, 1965,1976-77, 219251 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Receptions, 1915-17, 219250 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - College Women's Club of Houston, 1925, 1930, 219249 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - DePelchin Faith Home materials, 1977, 219248 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Children's report cards, 219247 (Box 54, Folder -)
  - Malcolm Lovett: Camp Dixie, 1916, 219246 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Adelaide Lovett: School materials, 1916-17, 219245 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Adelaide Lovett: wedding gift list, 219244 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Alexander Lovett: Hospitalization, 1939 (restricted), 219243 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Alexander Lovett: Sheppard & Enoch Pratt Hospital, June 1939-April 1941, Nov. 1950 (restricted), 219242 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Alexander Lovett: Sheppard & Enoch Pratt Hospital statements, 1939-1941 (restricted), 219241 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Alexander Lovett: misc., 219240 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Lovett: personal, 219239 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Family genealogy, ca. 1940, 219238 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - War Council Executive Committee minutes, 1917, 219237 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Furniture list (E.O. Lovett), 219236 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Stored furniture lists, 219235 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Edgar Odell Lovett funeral-related materials (memorials, flowers, thank you lists), 1957, 219234 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Death, Mary Hale Lovett, 1952, 219233 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Stationery samples, 1952, n.d., 219232 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 219231 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - No-Tsu-Ho Carnival 1911: photos (2) of Malcolm Lovett and Ruth Baker, King & Queen of Flower Carnival, 219230 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - No-Tsu-Ho Carnival 1911: photo of Miss Carter, Carnival Queen, 219229 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Black velvet cape worn by Mary Hale Lovett on World Tour, 219228 (Box 58, Folder -)
  - Commencement hoods worn by E.O. Lovett from Bethany College, Colorado College, Princeton and Tulane, 219227 (Box 59, Folder -)
  - Clothing worn by E.O. Lovett: socks, vests, spats, scarf, 219226 (Box 60, Folder -)
  - Flags, 219225 (Box 61, Folder -)
  - Artworks collected by Lovett Family, and E.O. Lovett tribute, 219224 (Box 62, Folder -)
  - Dance cards, Bible, ROTC pins, Locks of E.O. Lovett and Mrs. E.O. Lovett's hair, 219223 (Box 63, Folder -)
  - E. O. Lovett's academic regalia, 219222 (Box 64, Folder -)
  - E. O. Lovett's coat and vest, 219221 (Box 65, Folder -)
  - E. O. Lovett's top hat and carrying case., 219220 (Box 66, Folder -)
  - Oversize scrapbook of Maj. Henry S. Hale, including photocopies and color scans of 4 pages, 219219 (Box -, Folder -)
  - 3 suitcases belonging to E.O. Lovett, 219218 (Box -, Folder -)
  - Framed oil painting: "Autumns in Kentucky," ca. 1894 by Robert Burns Wilson (in care of Campus Art Committee), 219217 (Box -, Folder -)
  - Certificates of appreciation (2) Rice Institute to E.O. Lovett (upright picture case #27 and #28), 219216 (Box -, Folder -)
  - Framed oil painting: Mary Ellen Hale Lovett by Auguste Leroux, ca. 1924 (51 5.8" x 38 1/2"), 219215 (Box -, Folder -)
- Series VII: Addenda, 1892-1952, 218782
  - Correspondence, 219174
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1892-1894.; 219213 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1895-1896.; 219212 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1897.; 219211 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, June-Dec. 1897.; 219210 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1898, 219209 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1899, 219208 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1900-1901, 219207 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1902-1903, 219206 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1904, 219205 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, March-October 1905, 219204 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1905-1906, 219203 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Woodrow Wilson Correspondence. To Edgar O. Lovett, 1905, 1913-1915, 219202 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1907, 219201 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1908-1909, 219200 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1911-1914, 219199 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1915-1916, 219198 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1917-1918, 219197 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1919, 219196 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1920-April 1921, 219195 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, May-July 1921, 219194 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, Aug.-Dec. 1921, 219193 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1922-1924, 1927, 219192 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, July-Sept. 1928, 219191 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, Oct.-Dec. 1928, 219190 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1929-1936, 219189 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, Jan.-July 1937, 219188 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, Aug.-Dec. 1937, 219187 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1938, 219186 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1939, 219185 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1940, 219184 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Responses to social invitations, April-May 20, 1942, 219183 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Responses to social invitations, May 21-29, 1942, 219182 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1941-1943, 219181 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1944-1945, 219180 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, 1946, 1950, 1952, 219179 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Packet of Letters to Lovett Family, re: Theodore Hale's death, 1947, 219178 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Letters from Lawrence A. Lovett to Father, from Mexico, 1952, 219177 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, undated; Folder 1 of 2, 219176 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - To Edgar O. Lovett, undated; Folder 2 of 2, 219175 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Mary Hale Lovett, 219108
    - To Mary Hale [Lovett], 1889-1891, 219173 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - To Mary Hale, Jan.-June 1892, 219172 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - To Mary Hale, July-Sept. 1892, 219171 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - To Mary Hale, Oct.-Dec. 1892, 219170 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - To Mary Hale, 1892 [n.d.], 219169 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - To Mary Hale, Jan. 1893, 219168 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - To Mary Hale, Feb. 1893, 219167 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - To Mary Hale, Mar. 1893, 219166 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - To Mary Hale, Apr. 1893, 219165 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - To Mary Hale, May 1893, 219164 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - To Mary Hale, May 1893, 219163 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - To Mary Hale, July 1893, 219162 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - To Mary Hale, Aug. 1893, 219161 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - To Mary Hale, Sept.-Oct. 1893, 219160 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - To Mary Hale, Nov.-Dec. 1893, 219159 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - To Mary Hale, Jan.-Mar. 1894, 219158 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - To Mary Hale, Apr.-Aug. 1894, 219157 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - To Mary Hale, July-Sept. 1894, 219156 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - To Mary Hale, Oct.-Dec. 1894, 219155 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - To Mary Hale, Jan.-Mar. 1895, 219154 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - To Mary Hale, Apr.-Nov. 1895, 219153 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - To Mary Hale, 1896-1897, 219152 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1898, 219151 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1899, 219150 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1900, 219149 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1901-1902, 219148 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1903, 219147 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, re: social invit. 1904, 219146 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1904, 219145 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, re: social invit. 1905, 219144 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1905, 219143 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1906-1908, 1911, 219142 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - E.O. Lovett Math Papers dated 1894, returned to Mrs. Lovett in 1912, 219141 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1914, 219140 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1915-1917, 219139 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1918-1920, 219138 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, Jan.-Mar.1921, 219137 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, Apr.-Jun. 1921, 219136 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, July-Dec. 1921, 219135 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, Jan.-May 1922, 219134 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, July-Dec. 1922, 219133 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1923, 219132 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, Jan.-Oct. 1924, 219131 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, Nov.-Dec. 1924, 219130 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1925 (Mlle. Boulanger), 219129 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1925-1926, 219128 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1927-June 1928, 219127 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, July-Oct. 1928, 219126 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1929-Apr. 1931, 219125 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, May-Dec. 1931, 219124 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1932, 219123 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1933, 219122 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1934, 219121 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1938, 1940, n.d., 219120 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1935, 219119 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1936, 219118 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Samuel Bell Thomas corresp., 1936, 219117 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1937-1938, 219116 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1939, 219115 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1940-1943, 219114 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1944, 219113 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1945, 219112 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, 1946-1951, 219111 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - To Mary Hale Lovett, undated, 219110 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - To Mary Hale [Lovett], undated, 219109 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Dr. and Mrs. E.O. Lovett, 219095
    - To Dr. and Mrs. E.O. Lovett, 1897-1904, 219107 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - To Dr. and Mrs. E.O. Lovett, 1905, 219106 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - To Dr. and Mrs. E.O. Lovett, 1906-1908, undated, 219105 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - To Dr. and Mrs. E.O. Lovett, 1914-1936, 219104 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Packet: "1940 Garden Party Replies", 219103 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - To Dr. and Mrs. E.O. Lovett, 1930, 1941, 219102 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - To Dr. and Mrs. E.O. Lovett, 1942-1947, 219101 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Christmas cards to Dr. and Mrs. E.O. Lovett, 1948 (folder 1 of 2), 219100 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Christmas cards to Dr. and Mrs. E.O. Lovett, 1948 (folder 2 of 2), 219099 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - To Dr. and Mrs. E.O. Lovett, 1950, 219098 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - To Dr. and Mrs. E.O. Lovett, undated, 219097 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Fragments, 219096 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Lovett children, 219082
    - To Adelaide Lovett, 1903, 1911-1913, 219094 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - To Adelaide Lovett, 1914, 219093 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - To Adelaide Lovett, 1915, 219092 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - To Adelaide Lovett, 1919-1921, 219091 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - To Adelaide Lovett Baker, 1922-1923, 1932, 219090 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - From Adelaide Lovett Baker, undated, 219089 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - To H. Malcom Lovett (Europe), Jan.-Aug. 1921, 219088 (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - To H. Malcolm Lovett, 1913-1919, 219087 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - To H. Malcolm Lovett, 1928, 219086 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - To H. Malcolm Lovett, 1942, undated, 219085 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - To Lawrence Alexander Lovett, 1919-1925, 219084 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Lawrence Alexander Lovett, undated, 219083 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Hale family, 219031
    - Hale letters, 1865-1866, 219081 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Bell-Gregory letters, 219080 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - To Virginia Adelaide Gregory Hale, 219079 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Gregory estate correspondence, 219078 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - From Henry S. Hale, 1865, 219077 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - To Mrs. Henry S. Hale, 1890-1899, 219076 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - To Mrs. Henry S. Hale, 1900-1901, 219075 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - To Mrs. Henry S. Hale, 1902-1907, 219074 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - To Mrs. Henry S. Hale, 1908-1909, 219073 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - To Mrs. Henry S. Hale, 1910-1911, 219072 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - To Mrs. Henry S. Hale, 1912, 219071 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - To Mrs. Henry S. Hale, 1913-1914, undated, 219070 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - To Maj. H.S. Hale, 1876, 219069 (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - To Maj. H.S. Hale, 1890-1900, 219068 (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - To Maj. H.S. Hale, 1901-1910, 219067 (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - To Maj. H.S. Hale, 1911-1912, 219066 (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - To Maj. H.S. Hale, 1913-1914, 219065 (Box 74, Folder 22)
    - To Maj. H.S. Hale, 219064 (Box 74, Folder 23)
    - To Maj. and Mrs. H.S. Hale, 219063 (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - To Henry S. Hale, Jr., 219062 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - To Lindsay Hale, 219061 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - To Mrs. Lindsay Hale, 219060 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - To Theodore Hale, 219059 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - To Rex Hale, 219058 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - To Sam Thomas, 219057 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - To Mrs. James A. Baker, 219056 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Packet of letters from Mrs. Mary Lovett, 219055 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - To Hale family members, 219054 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - To Unknown (Hale Family) recipients, 219053 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Packet: Letters to Hale Family Members, Re: death of Major H.S. Hale, 1922, 219052 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - To Miss Annie Hale, 1886-1889, 219051 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - To Miss Annie Hale, 1890-1891, 219050 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - To Miss Annie Hale, 1892, 219049 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - To Miss Annie Hale, Jan.-Jun. 1893, 219048 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - To Miss Annie Hale, July-Dec. 1893, 219047 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - To Miss Annie Hale, 1894-1899, 219046 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Packet: "Annie B. Hale's foreign letters to family," 1900, 219045 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Packet: "Annie B. Hale Paris Correspondence Pads and Clippings," 1900, 219044 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - To Miss Annie Hale, 1900-1901, 219043 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - To Miss Annie Hale, 1902, 219042 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - To Miss Annie Hale, 1903, 219041 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - To Miss Annie Hale, 1904-1906, 219040 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - To Miss Annie Hale, 1907, 219039 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - To Miss Annie Hale, 1908, 219038 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - To Miss Annie Hale, 1909, 219037 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - To Miss Annie Hale, 1910, 219036 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - To Miss Annie Hale, 1911-1912, 219035 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - To Miss Annie Hale, undated, 219034 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Misc. correspondents, 219033 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - From Mme. Emile Bertauy, 1922, 219032 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, 218989
    - Adelaide Lovett, 219030 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Adelaide Lovett-Rice commencement 1920, 219029 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Adelaide and Browne Baker family, 1900-1942, 219028 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Ellen Kennedy Lovett, June 1906, 219027 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Henry Malcolm Lovett family, 219026 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Lawrence Alexander Lovett, 219025 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Lovett children, 219024 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Major H.S. Hale, 219023 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Mary Hale Lovett, 219022 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Mary Hale Lovett, E.O. Lovett, and Annie Hale, Paris 1900, 219021 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Mary Hale and Adelaide; Mary Hale and friends, 219020 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Mary Hale Lovett [McLean], 1937, 1944, 219019 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - E.O. Lovett at Bethany College, c. 1889, 219018 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - E.O. Lovett and friends, c. 1889, 219017 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - E.O. Lovett, 219016 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Lovett family groups, 219015 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Family photos, 1915-, 219014 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - N.A. Hale, 219013 (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Major H.S. Hale residence, Mayfield, Kentucky, 219012 (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - Hale family groups, 219011 (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - Hale family plot, Mayfield, KY, cemetery, 219010 (Box 77, Folder 21)
    - Hale relations, 219009 (Box 77, Folder 22)
    - Gregory family, 219008 (Box 77, Folder 23)
    - Murray-Hale relatives, KY, 219007 (Box 77, Folder 24)
    - Maj. Hale and staff at Treasurer's Office, pre-1900, 219006 (Box 77, Folder 25)
    - Mayfield, KY Friends, 219005 (Box 77, Folder 26)
    - Lovett House, Princeton, NJ, 219004 (Box 77, Folder 27)
    - Observatory House, Princeton, NJ, 219003 (Box 77, Folder 28)
    - Princeton University, 219002 (Box 77, Folder 29)
    - Rice Institute construction, 1911, 219001 (Box 77, Folder 30)
    - Rice Institute, 1937, 219000 (Box 77, Folder 31)
    - Rice Institute, 1912-1918, 218999 (Box 77, Folder 32)
    - Rice Institute, 1945, 218998 (Box 77, Folder 33)
    - Rice Institute groups, 218997 (Box 77, Folder 34)
    - Plaza Hotel, Houston, 218996 (Box 77, Folder 35)
    - University of Virginia, 1897 (folder 1 of 3), 218995 (Box 77, Folder 36)
    - University of Virginia, 1897 (folder 1 of 3), 218994 (Box 77, Folder 37)
    - University of Virginia, 1897 (folder 3 of 3), 218993 (Box 77, Folder 38)
    - Other family photos, 1900-1914, 218992 (Box 77, Folder 39)
    - Unidentified, 218991 (Box 77, Folder 40)
    - Photographic negatives, 218990 (Box 77, Folder 41)
  - Memorabilia, 218839
    - Mary Lovett-Engagement books, 1904, 218988 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Mary Lovett Appointment book, 1909-1912, 218987 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Mary Lovett-Diary of trip around the world, 1908-1909, 218986 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Mary Lovett-Diary and lists re: parents' deaths, 1912-1914, 218985 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - "Birds I have seen" journal, 1901/ Mary Lovett account ledger, 1912-1916, 218984 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Mary Lovett-Daily log with articles, 1913-1914, 218983 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Mary Lovett Diary, 1916, 218982 (Box 78, Folder 7)